import 'package:Gem_Quest/quiz.dart';

  List<QuizQuestion> hardQuestions = [
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'What is the chemical formula for emerald?',
      answers: ['Be3Al2Si6O18', 'Al2O3', 'SiO2', 'C'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    ),
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'What is the rarest gemstone in the world?',
      answers: ['Tanzanite', 'Painite', 'Alexandrite', 'Red Beryl'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    ),
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'Which gemstone is known as "foolâ€™s gold" due to its metallic luster?',
      answers: ['Pyrite', 'Hematite', 'Citrine', 'Sphalerite'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    ),
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'What optical phenomenon causes a star-like pattern to appear in some gemstones?',
      answers: ['Asterism', 'Chatoyancy', 'Iridescence', 'Adularescence'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    ),
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'Which gemstone is composed of hydrated silica and contains up to 20% water?',
      answers: ['Opal', 'Moonstone', 'Chalcedony', 'Topaz'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    ),
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'Which rare gemstone is only found near Mount Kilimanjaro in Tanzania?',
      answers: ['Tanzanite', 'Zoisite', 'Peridot', 'Tourmaline'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    ),
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'What is the specific gravity range of diamond?',
      answers: ['3.5-3.6', '2.5-2.7', '4.0-4.1', '3.0-3.2'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    ),
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'What impurity causes the pink color in pink diamonds?',
      answers: ['Boron', 'Nitrogen', 'Plastic deformation', 'Iron'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    ),
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'Which gemstone is traditionally associated with the zodiac sign of Pisces?',
      answers: ['Aquamarine', 'Amethyst', 'Turquoise', 'Moonstone'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    ),
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'What is the fluorescence color of natural Burmese rubies under UV light?',
      answers: ['Red', 'Blue', 'Green', 'White'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    ),
  ];
